瞧瞧这些人
Look at all these people
也不给小费 就会坐在那里
just sitting here and not tipping,
啪啪啪地玩电脑
working on their computers.
这家伙有一台全新的苹果电脑
This guy has a brand-new Apple.
而老娘同一个苹果啃了快一周
I've been eating the same apple for a week.
都怪史蒂夫·乔布斯[有工作]
I blame Steve Jobs.
这些人更像是"史蒂夫·没工作吧"
These people are more like Steve-I-have-no-jobs.
好吧 真是够了
All right, that's it.
厄尔 给我无线路由器
Earl, I need to get the wireless router.
原来那玩意是干这个的啊
Oh, is that what this is?
我还以为是饼干加热器呢
I thought it was a cookie-warmer.
听着 你们这些蹭网客
Attention deadbeat diners.
你们不能点杯咖啡 就赖一整晚
You can't just sit here all night and only order coffee.
这又不是星巴克
This is not a Starbucks.
而且一看我们这里不卖
And I know that because we don't sell
诺拉·琼斯的CD或是香蕉就知道
Norah Jones cds or bananas.
这是能提供无线网络的路由器
This is the router for the free wi-fi.
而这位是需要挣点小费的服务员
And that is a waitress who needs to make some tips.
说真的 伙计们 我要的是钞票
Seriously, guys, I need actual cash.
那家伙居然想用创意来付账
This guy just offered to pay me in ideas.
如果我拔掉这个插头 网络就会没掉
If I pull this plug, the internet will go down.
而你
And you--
写给前男友的可怜兮兮电邮会没掉
that sad email you're in the middle of writing to your ex-boyfriend,
反正你也不应该发给他
the one you shouldn't send anyway--gone.
而你
And you--
花费了三小时
That vaguely pornographic anime film
非法下载的色情动漫 也会没掉
you've been illegally downloading for the past three hours-gone.
而你 埋头写的破剧本
And you--that screenplay you've been writing,
你可以继续写 不过我们都知道结局
you can keep working on it, but we all know how it ends:
就是你搬回去跟你老妈住
with you moving back in with your mother.
现在谁想点餐呀
Now, who's gonna order?
很好 我去拿菜单
Great, I'll go get some menus.
给 卡洛琳 把这个放回去
Here, Caroline, put this back.
可惜了我的饼干加热器
Ooh, my cookie-warmer.
第10桌刚点了杯鸡尾酒
Table ten just ordered cocktails.
她以为我们这里有多高级啊
Yeah, 'cause we're that kind of a place.
谁知道"性感沙滩"怎么做呀
Does anyone know how to make Sex On The Beach?
很简单
Easy.
我穿上三角泳裤 之后就能了
I put on my speedo and wait.
那俩妞喝酒喝好久了
Those girls have been drinking for hours.
随便加饮料 然后混朗姆酒就行了
Just press every button on the gun and add rum.
瞧瞧她们 无忧无虑
Look at them. Not a care in the world.
开心自在
Having a great time.
-我讨厌她们 -我也讨厌她们
- I hate them. - I hate them, too.
我比你更讨厌她们
I hate them more.
我讨厌你比我更讨厌她们
I hate that you hate them more.
羡慕嫉妒恨啊
So jealous.
好了 四人座准备好了
Okay, ready for party of four.
借过 抱歉
Excuse me. Pardon me.
借过 好了
Excuse me. Okay.
宝贝
Hey, baby!
-美呆了 -向来如此
- Looking good. - Mm, always.
我就坐我老位子
I'll be in my booth.
苏菲 你不能一个人占四个人的座位
Sophie, you cannot take up a whole booth alone.
有人等着呢 你得离开
There are people waiting. You must leave.
快给我滚去墙角罚站
Go stand in the corner now!
不然我就当着全班同学的面
Before I bend you across my knee and spank you
把你按在我膝盖上打屁股
in front of the whole class.
我本来就要去角落里站着
Well, I was going to stand in the corner anyway.
不过明晚 你只能坐小桌子
But tomorrow night, smaller table.
快给我滚去墙角罚站
Go stand in the corner now!
好了 我现在不羡慕她们了
Okay, I'm over being jealous of them.
还在笑 她们干嘛呢
Still? What are they--
都夹着根电动棒吗
Sitting on vibrators?
别管她们了
Let it go.
她们才没那么爽呢
They're not having that good of a time.
不 麦克斯 是我们没那么爽
No, Max, we're not having that good of a time.
我们只能埋头工作
All we do is work.
上次不上班出去玩是什么时候的事了
When's the last time we took a day and just had fun?
那两个白痴让我想起
I mean, those two idiots remind me
以前我跟闺蜜下馆子
how much fun it was when I'd go out to lunch
边吃午饭边喝鸡尾酒
and have cocktails with my girlfriends
看着她们假装吃饭的好时光
and watch them pretend to eat.
你是想找我白天喝酒吧
I think you're talking about day-drinking,
我喜欢
And I think I like it.
好吧 那我们得好好玩玩
All right, let's do something fun.
我会系上领带 穿上帅气背心
I'll put on my bolo tie and my best vest
然后带我的妞下馆子
and take my girl out to eat.
你带我去的是什么餐厅
So, what is this lunch spot you're taking me to?
法国餐厅吗
Is it french?
你觉得主厨会送咱们一份开胃菜吗
Do you think the chef will send an amuse-bouche to the table?
不会 不过今早我"那里"剃了个笑脸出来
No, but this morning I shaved a smiley face into my bush,
也很开怀哦
and it's very amusing.
你知道吗
You know what?
盛装打扮一番
It's just so fun to get dressed up
然后让别人来服务我们 真的很好玩
and have someone wait on us for a change.
我还特意从"装腰店"买了一双新的连裤袜
I even bought new panty hose from dooahnay rayahdey.
你是说药妆店吧
You mean Duane Reade?
那店是这么叫的吗
Oh, is that how you pronounce it?
我们到了 快去排队
Well, we're here. Better get in line.
哇 还要排队 很受欢迎嘛
Oh, there's a line. Popular place.
餐厅名叫什么
What's the name?
"施粥坊" 名字真可爱
"Soup kitchen." That's a cute name.
有威廉斯堡的穷酸感
Very Williamsburg.
感觉像"老板故意把高档小餐馆
Like, "let's take our upscale urban bistro
弄得像是为大众开放的食物救济站
"and make it seem like it's just a soup kitchen open to everyone,
但其实不然"
but it's not really a soup kitchen."
真好 这家店的厕所谁都能用
Oh, that's nice. They let them use the bathroom.
桌子也谁都能坐
And sit at a table.
天啊 这就是一家食物救济站
Oh, my god! This is really a soup kitchen.
你说请我吃饭 就是来这里吃吗
This is your idea of treating me to lunch?
我们又不是无家可归的人
We're not homeless.
但我们是无汤可喝的人啊
No, but we are soup-less.
而且又不是只有无家可归的人来这里吃饭
And it's not just homeless people who eat here.
好吧 或许他们是主要客群
Okay, maybe they're the target audience.
瞧 这里还有很多其他人
Look, there's a lot of other people
也没钱下馆子吃饭
who can't afford to go out to eat.
你说得对
You're right.
为什么这里这么多嬉皮士
Why are there so many hipsters here?
因为这里不但有没工作的人
Because this place isn't just for people who don't have jobs,
也有不想工作的人
it's for people who don't want them.
好吧 闻起来还不错
Well, it does smell good.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我们想看看你的午餐菜单
We'd like to take a look at your lunch menu.
菜单每天都在变
Menu changes every day.
而且我们这里没菜单
Also, there is no menu.
这里只有四种菜
There's, like, four things.
那好吧 你有什么好建议
Oh, okay. So what do you recommend?
要听听我的建议吗
Oh, what do I recommend?
别共用针头 记得要戴套[预防艾滋病]
Don't share needles, and and use condoms.
不能跟人说我教你们戴套哦
But you didn't hear that last one from me.
修女可以这么毒舌的吗
Are nuns even allowed to be sarcastic?
如果可以 那我要认真思考下未来的职业了
If they are, I have some serious thinking to do about my future.
这个碎牛肉三明治[邋遢乔]是我吃过
This sloppy joe is the most amazing
最好吃的糟糕食物
terrible thing I've ever eaten.
我超喜欢它是先被人"嚼"碎的
I love that it's basically pre-chewed,
所以不必费劲嚼 直接咽下去就行
so all you really have to do is swallow.
好吃死了
So good,
我小时候每天都吃
I used to have these every day when I was a kid.
那你小时候过得也不算太悲催嘛
Well, then I guess your childhood wasn't all that bad.
我们买不起真正的碎牛肉堡
We couldn't afford the real Manwich mix,
所以我妈的男朋友 脏人卡尔
so my mom's boyfriend, dirty Carl,
就会给我们带回别人吃剩的肉渣
used to bring us leftover meat scraps
然后用他在废车场的烂车里捡来的
and then bash 'em together with old ketchup packets
旧番茄酱包搅拌到一起
he'd found in cars at the junkyard.
我明白你为什么会觉得这里是好餐馆了
Now I understand why you think this is a nice restaurant.
你有注意到喝得越多
Have you noticed the more you drink,
这地方就变得越美好吗
the better this place gets?
我倒是注意到喝得越多
I've noticed the more I drink,
一切都变得越美好
the better everything gets.
为什么我们不每天都喝酒呢
Why don't we drink every day?
我就是啊
Some of we do.
我玩得很开心
I'm having a great time.
谢谢你 麦克斯
Thank you, Max.
昨天你还为自己的生活感到失落
Well, yesterday, you were so bummed about your life,
我就想把你带去
I thought I'd take you somewhere
能让你自我感觉良好的地方
you could feel good about yourself.
好吧 有句话我想说很久了
Okay, I've been wanting to say this the whole time.
我觉得我们是这里最正点的人
I feel like we're the hottest people in this room.
-这么说是不是很坏啊 -是呀
- Is that terrible? - Yes.
说到正点的人...
Speaking of hot people...
慢着
Wait.
是我们喝醉了 还是我们终于
Are we drunk or do we finally have one brain
对男人的口味变得一致了
and the same taste in guys?
我也不知道
I don't know,
但这里突然成了我最喜欢的新餐馆
but this is suddenly my new favorite restaurant.
走 咱们去来个"人肉三明治"
Let's go get ourselves some of that man-wich.
我有点喜欢"醉鬼卡洛琳"
I kind of like "drunk Caroline"
多于其他时候的卡洛琳
way more than the other Caroline.
我也有点更喜欢这样的她呢
I kind of like her better, too.
打扰了 修女
Excuse me, sisters.
你认识刚刚进来的那个男的吗
Do you know the guy who just came in here?
-长得帅的那个 -他超帅的 对不对
- The cute one. - He's so cute, right?
他叫安迪
His name is Andy,
他刚在对面开了一家糖果店
and he just opened a candy store across the way.
不是吧 糖果
Shut up! Candy?
我超爱糖果的
I love candy.
提问
Question:
什么能让今天更美好点
what would make this day even better?
糖果
Candy?
你真应该去追那个帅哥
You should totally go for the hot guy.
或者应该你去追他
Or you can go for him.
咱们考虑一下
Let's think about this.
他身家清白 又不吸毒
He's clean and not a drug addict,
所以更适合我
so he's more my type.
他有一整店的糖果和一根肉棒
Well, he's got a store full of candy and a penis,
所以更适合我
so he's more my type.
不然这样
You know what?
你去追 我让给你
Go for it. You've got dibs.
-麦克斯 你真好 -当然
- Aww, that's so nice of you, Max. - Yeah,
当你在后面跟他翻云覆雨时
and while you're doing him in the back room,
我会顺点糖果进口袋
I'll be pocketing some candy.
别呀 关门了
Oh, no. It's closed.
麦克斯 你知道做什么会好玩吗
Hey, Max, you know what'd be fun?
用那个垃圾桶砸烂他的前窗吗
If we threw that trash can through the front window?
我本来是想给他留张纸条
I was gonna say we should leave him a note.
而且砸垃圾桶有什么好玩的
And what would be fun about throwing that can through a window?
你试过吗 超好玩的
Have you ever done it? It's fun!
牌子翻过来了
Oh, the sign's turned around.
他能看见我们
He can see us.
他在冲着我们微笑呢
He's smiling at us.
我们该进去吗
Should we go in?
如果我小时候有学到什么
If I learned anything as a child,
那就是陌生人要请你吃糖时
it's when a stranger offers you candy,
你一定要接受
you say yes.
你好
Hi.
我们看到牌子 还以为你关门了呢
We thought the sign said you were closed.
对 我翻过来了 我想你们进来
Yeah, I turned it around. I wanted you guys to come in.
* 跟我来 *
* Come with me *
* 你将置身于 *
* and you'll be *
* 梦想中的世界 *
* in world of pure imagination *
如果你们不喜欢这歌
If this isn't your thing,
我还有些重金属和朋克音乐
I also have some sabbath and some beastie boys.
如果这里是"糖果安迪的糖果盛宴"
So, if this is "Candy Andy's sweets and treats,"
请问你是糖果安迪吗
Are you Candy Andy?
拜托 我们还不熟
Oh, please. We hardly know each other.
请叫我糖德鲁·安德鲁
Call me Candrew Andrew.
我是卡洛琳 她是麦克斯
I'm Caroline, and this is Max.
麦克斯 说话啊
Max, say something.
失语中 这一切太美好了
Can't. It's all too wonderful.
瞧瞧这小地方塞满了糖果
Look at all the candy crammed in this little space.
我们仿佛来到了威利·旺卡的结肠
It's like we're inside Willy Wonka's colon.
谢谢
Thanks.
没错 我就是想要这种效果
Yeah, it's kind of the look I was going for too.
我之所以布置得这么到位
And I know it's accurate
是因为有奥柏伦柏人帮我
because I had the Oompa Loompas help me.
他们工钱很高
They were expensive,
但你能怎么办呢
but what are you gonna doom-pa-dee-doo?
通常成交或者做完事 我会按一下铃
Normally I'd ring the bell after something that golden,
但我不想吓着你
but I don't want to scare you.
你说完 没听到我会好奇死的
Well, now I have to hear the bell.
这下我心愿达成了
Now that's all I want to hear.
你这里提供免费试吃吗
Do you do free samples?
看样子是有
You do, by the way.
我带你们都尝尝 免费的
Let me hook you guys up. On the house.
快嫁给他
Marry this guy right now.
这家店很小 我能听见哦
It's a small store. I can hear you.
很好 这样你们进展能快点
Good. Moves things along faster.
有空来威廉斯堡餐厅坐坐
Hey, come by the Williamsburg diner sometime.
我们在那里打工
We work there.
我们免费请你试吃
We'll give you free samples of food
压根不值得付钱的餐
You shouldn't have to pay for anyway.
你们怎么会来这一带呢
So, what brings you in to this neighborhood?
我们来吃...
Oh, we were having lunch at the--
你这里真是太有爱了
This ...is a really adorable space.
谢谢
Thank you.
我对糖果一直很有爱
You know, candy is my passion.
是有点怪 但我一直都爱
Yeah, I said it. Always has been.
小时候玩玩具 就爱让特种部队玩具
Even as a kid, I would have my G.I. Joes
卖糖给变形金刚玩具
sell Sweet Tarts to my Transformers.
橡皮软糖 小熊软糖 小虫软糖
Gum drops, gummy bears, gummy worms,
热狗软糖 披萨软糖
gummy hot dogs, gummy pizza.
看得我都软糖高潮了
Ooh, I just had a gummy-gasm.
你小时候最喜欢什么糖果呢
So what was your favorite candy as a kid?
我小时候没怎么吃糖呢
Actually, I didn't eat a lot of candy as a child.
看在你漂亮 刚我就当没听到
Okay, I'm gonna overlook that because you're pretty,
有空一起喝杯咖啡
but maybe we could talk about
聊聊你的悲惨童年如何
your terrible childhood over coffee sometime.
答应啦
Yeah?
要不是糖果太诱人
I'd leave you two alone,
我早闪开让你们俩"独处"了
if this place wasn't filled with candy.
-那你最喜欢什么口味 -椰子
-Okay, so what's your favorite flavor? - Coconut.
容我看看C区[coconut椰子]
And I'm walking to the "C"S.
糖果还按照首字母排列的吗
The candy's alphabetical?
-我现在也要嫁你了 -好的
- Now I'm marrying you too. - Okay.
椰香西瓜糖
Let's see. Seconut watermelon slice.
这个如何
How's that sound?
不太好
Um, not so good.
可以别再提糖果了吗
Actually, please don't say anything more about candy.
这里是不是很热啊
Is it hot in here?
才不会 是很棒才对
No, it's awesome in here.
波士顿闷烤豆
Boston baked beans?
我到20岁才知道他们是真的豆子
Didn't know they weren't real beans till I was 20.
别说了
Please stop.
这里面是不是有点冷啊
Is it cold in here?
这里是不是又冷又热啊
Is it hot and cold in here?
麦克斯 我有种怪怪的感觉
Max, I feel weird.
别紧张 是你的"小妹妹"在从冬眠中醒来
Relax, it's just your lady parts waking up from hibernation.
店小 都听得见哟
Again, small store. Can hear everything.
对不起 请见谅
I am so sorry. Pardon me.
你没事吧
Oh, uh, are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
麦克斯 我有事
Max, I am not fine.
再两秒我就要成"邋遢乔安"了
I'm gonna be sloppy Joanne in about two seconds.
店真的很小
Tiny, tiny store.
你要用...
Do you need to use the--
不必不必 我们挺好
No. We're fine.
我们要先走了 再见
We'll just be going. Nice to meet you.
不行 来不及了 洗手间在...
Nope, I'm not gonna make it. Where is the--
就在那边
Right--right there.
她肯定没事的
I'm sure she'll be all right.
我先去外面站会
I'm just gonna step outside.
听到呕吐声让我也想...
The sound of someone throwing up makes me--
我刚也忍着不跟着吐很久了
Oh, dude, I've been trying to not throw up this whole time.
刚里边是发生了什么事了呀
Whew, what happened there, right?
你好点了吗
Feeling better?
她有跟你说她吐了一地的东西
Did she tell you she projectile-puked soup and sloppy seconds
在人家帅哥的店里吗
all over a really cute guy and his floor?
我这么说吧 卡洛琳
Let me put it this way, Caroline.
在我还吸海洛因那会 首次约会
In my heroin days, that would have been
发生这档事都还不算糟呢
a perfectly acceptable first date.
我就不懂了
I don't understand it.
我们吃了一样的东西
We ate the exact same thing.
你怎么吃了一点事都没有
How could you have not have gotten sick?
你大小姐的胃吃不惯
You must still have "rch girl" stomach.
但我穷人的胃早吃惯了
I'm used to poor food.
你吃了要病 我吃还能皮肤变好呢
What made you sick made my skin clear up.
-姑娘们 -你好啊 苏菲
- Hi, girls. - Hey, Sophie.
我坐我老位子
I'll be in my booth.
奇了怪了
Well, this is weird.
算了 不知者无罪
It's okay. You didn't know.
下不为例
Don't let it happen again.
好了 你们走吧
Okay, good-bye now.
苏菲 你刚是在干啥呢
Sophie, what do you think you're doing?
怎么 他们坐了我的卡座
What? They were sitting in my booth.
才不是你的 卡座是我的
It is not your booth, it's my booth.
如果是你的卡座 怎么没有儿童垫高椅呢
If it was your booth, wouldn't it have a booster seat?
苏菲你想玩 我陪你玩到底
Oh, Sophie wants to dance? We gonna dance.
麦克斯
Max. Hi.
是我 安迪 糖果店的
It's Andy. From the store.
让你偷拿一管口红糖
The guy who let you walk out
而不逮住你的店老板
with a push pop in your pocket.
那一根可不是"口红糖" 安迪
That wasn't a Push Pop, Andy.
很高兴再见
I was happy to see you.
那你现在要更高兴了
Well, you're gonna be even happier in a minute.
爽耶
Yay!
我这是先礼后兵
But these come with a catch.
我邀请你跟卡洛琳
Invites for Caroline and you
来参加我店里的派对
to a party at my candy store.
来的时候还是别穿这身制服吧
But maybe don't wear that uniform.
会被误认是人形"蜜糖老爹"糖[黄色包装]
People are gonna think you're a giant Sugar Daddy.
她还吐着呢
So, she's still going at it, huh?
这么瘦的姑娘
Such a skinny girl.
还有多少能吐啊
How much more can come out of her?
不是啦 她是有点羞于见你
Nah, she's just a little embarrassed.
自尊之类的事情在作怪吧
Something about self-esteem. I don't know.
她老把自尊搞得煞有其事的
She throws it around like it means something.
我很希望她能来 别有压力
Well, I'd love her to come. No pressure.
但如果你能说服她来
But if you can talk her into it,
我就会请你吃糖
there'll be unlimited candy for you
免费吃到你死的那天
for the rest of your life.
看那男的 还抄袭我的招
Look at him, stealing my bit.
糖果男来邀请我们
The candy man came with invitations
去参加他店里的派对哟
to a party at his store.
你觉得我有可能不偷听你们对话吗
What, you think I wasn't listening at the door?
我全听到了
I heard everything.
挖苦我呕吐的话 也都听见了
All the vomit jokes. I heard them all.
都送我珠宝首饰啦
Jewelry, already?
你的新老公喜欢四处撒钱啊
Your new husband likes to throw the cash around.
他才不是我的新老公
He is not my new husband.
也没机会了
And now he never will be.
泡泡糖带呢
Ooh, bubble tape.
好不容易遇见了可爱嘴甜的男人
I finally meet an adorable, sweet guy.
他甜到都有一家
A guy so sweet, the word "sweet"
"甜"[糖]与他名字合一的店了
is next to his name on actual real estate.
但机会全都被我自己搞砸了
And I completely destroy any chance I have with him.
你什么都没搞砸啊
You didn't destroy anything.
而且让他一开始就知道
And it's good to let him know right off the bat
你容易"反胃想吐"也好[口交不便]
that you have a gag reflex.
承您吉言啊
Oh! Oh, that's lovely.
祝你情人节快乐好吧
Happy Valentines' day.
我死也不去那个派对
I am not going to that party.
我没脸再见他了
I can never see him again.
那你会介意我去吗
Well, do you mind if I still go?
在糖果店里待到午夜过后
Being in a candy store after midnight
是我死前愿望之一呢
is on my bucket list.
我以前还以为这是最不可能的一条呢
Funny, I thought that was the impossible one.
你去吧 玩得开心点
You should go. Have fun.
不去会损失很大哦
I think you're missing out,
你们俩可是天生一对
because you two are perfect for each other.
像童话《糖果屋》里的男女主
You're like Hansel and Gretel.
他们是兄妹好吗
They were brother and sister.
那又怎样
So?
卡洛琳不来啊
So, no Caroline, huh?
她来不了
Uh, no. She couldn't make it.
我好伤心啊
Well, I'm feeling very sad,
但你绝对看不出
but you'll never know it.
没事的啦
You're fine.
你的派对也不缺美女
You don't seem to be short on other female party guests.
她们就只是朋友啦
Oh, come on. They're fiends.
有些是附近住户
Some of them I know from the neighborhood.
有些是我在华尔街的老同事
Some I worked with on Wall Street.
华尔街啊
Wall Street?
你以前推糖果小车
Did you have a little candy tray
-在那一带叫卖吗 -我倒想
- you walked around with? - I wish.
那肯定很有意思
That would have been awesome.
我以前就坐在办公室里
I was stuck in an office pushing stock
替制药公司搞股票
in pharmaceutical companies.
等等
Wait.
你还认识能搞到"药"的人啊
You know people who have access to pills?
你棒得都要无极限了
And just when I thought you couldn't get any better.
然后 有天我去上班
Yeah, one day, I went into the firm,
发现没班上了
and there was no firm.
公司破产
Bankrupt. Boom.
没工作 没钱 全没了
End of job, no money. Nothing.
我连喝了一周闷酒后
And after I drank nonstop for a week,
灵光一闪 发现自己终于可以追梦了
I figured, hey, now I can do what I've always dreamed of.
开家糖果店 当自己的老板
Open a candy store, be my own boss.
我花光积蓄 开了这家糖果店
So I used all my savings and opened up this place.
要不了多久
And pretty soon,
糖果安迪将一统糖界天下
Candy Andy will rule the world of sweets and treats.
-会太臭屁吗 -不会
- That sound braggy? - No.
好啦 赶其他人回家吧
All right, kick everybody out,
然后跟我回家去
and let's go back to my place.
麦克斯 无意冒犯
Ah...Max, no offense,
但我喜欢的是你朋友
but I'm more into your friend.
安迪 无意冒犯
Um, Andy, no offense,
但我喜欢的是你的糖果
but I'm more into the candy than the Andy.
我想你来我家
I want you to come to my apartment
跟卡洛琳打个招呼
and say hey to Caroline.
我之前说的没错
I was right.
-你们两个是天生一对 -真的吗
- You two are perfect for each other. - Yeah?
反正这裤子也不沾到呕吐物
I mean, it would be nice to hang with her
趁机去找她也挺好
in pants I don't care about.
她不在家
She's not here.
可能是去遛马了
She must have taken the horse for a walk.
等等 你们有马啊
Wait, you have a horse,
你们居然不炫耀
And I'm just hearing about this now?
我只是开家糖果店
I have a candy store and it's out of my mouth,
就在初见30秒内炫耀了
in the first 30 seconds.
稍等一下 我尿个尿
Be right back. I have to pee.
她不会介意我来这里的吧
She'll be okay with me being here, right?
没事的 她羞愧而已 会过去的
Yeah, she was just embarrassed. She'll get over it.
你干嘛呢 先敲门呀
What are you doing? Knock first!
你双腿怎么开在空中啊
Why are your legs up in the air like that?
还有你为什么还把莲蓬头
And why were you holding the shower head
放到你下...
down by your- oh!
抱歉抱歉
I'm sorry.
我以为你会在家自怨自艾
I thought you'd be home feeling bad for yourself,
而不是自爽自嗨
not feeling your bad self.
你怎么这么早回家了
What are you doing home already?
你不是去糖果店的派对吗
Why aren't you at the Candy Andy party?
少用那鄙视的眼神
Oh, don't look at me like that.
搞得好像全世界
It's not like I'm the only person
只有我一个人会自慰
in the world who masturbates.
对了 安迪来了哦
Also, Andy's here.
我们想给你个惊喜
We wanted to surprise you.
你倒是给了我们个惊喜
But then you surprised us.
没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
很多人都发生过这尴尬事
That kind of situation happens to a lot of people.
谁 都谁发生过这种事了
Who? Who has that ever happened to?
现在提这个话题有点敏感
I know this might be a delicate area right now,
但我觉得以后咱们家的水费
but I'm thinking you should probably pay more
你得付一半以上
than half of our water bill.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我需要杯热茶暖暖身子
I need some hot tea to warm me up.
早先我想洗澡
There's no hot water in our building
发现我们大楼没热水了
when I tried to take a shower.
因为都跑进卡洛琳身体里了
That's because it's all in Caroline.
麦克斯
Max!
干嘛这么敏感啊
You are too tense.
来吧 来让你放松一下
Here. Take this and relax a little.
如何
Eh?
"舒缓"一点了吗
This doing anything for you?
我去坐我老位子了
Well, I'll be in my booth.
你好啊 苏菲
Hello, Sophie.
你在我的卡座里干啥呢
What are you doing in my booth?
才不是你的卡座 是我的卡座 还有
It's not your booth, it's my booth. And look.
其他卡座都被人占了
All the other booths are taken.
你得像其他独自前来的客人
So you'll have to sit at small table,
独自一人坐小桌子了
as is customary for lone diners.
这是我的专座
This is my booth.
没事 不知者无罪 你们走吧
It's okay, you didn't know. Okay, bye-bye now.
麦克斯 快看我的新专座
Hello, Max. Check out my new booth.
比旧的还棒呢
I think it's better.
惨了 我不想再见到他
Oh, no. I don't want to see him again.
他都已经看过你最坏的一面了
Look, he's already seen you at your worst.
你最惨也就呕吐跟自慰了
You vomited and masturbated. That's your full range.
你好啊
Hi.
我知道你肯定还觉得...
Look, I know you're really embarrassed about--
那些事丢人
Well, everything.
我也知道无论我说什么
And there's really nothing I can say
你还是会觉得丢人
to convince you not to be.
所以呢
So...
这下我也丢人了吧
Who's embarrassed now?
为了更丢人
And to further my embarrassment,
我将在公众场合做体操动作
I will now do gymnastics in public.
那才不丢人呢 根本帅呆了
That is not embarrassing. It was amazing.
好吧
All right.
那你跟我回家 我也自慰给你看
Well, then come back to my house and watch me masturbate.
也可以一起去喝杯咖啡
Or we could just get coffee.
-我好高兴哦 -谢了 麦克斯
- Yay, I'm so happy! - Thanks, Max.
不是替你高兴 是替自己
No, not for you. For me.
终身免费糖果 而且还可能有"药"
I'm getting unlimited candy and maybe some pills.